（夢子(ゆめこ)）おはようございます
Good morning.
（鈴井(すずい)）あっ 夢子
Yumeko!
何を見ていらっしゃるのですか？
What are you looking at?
（鈴井）あ… いや これは…
This is...
この子 現役インディーズ
アイドルでありながら
She's an indie idol
and a member of the student council too.
うちの生徒会役員でもあるんだ
（夢子）
まあ 生徒会にそのような方が
Oh, I didn't know there was someone
like that on the student council.
（鈴井）夢見弖(ゆめみて)ユメミ
Yumemi Yumemite.
２年生で役職は広報
She's a second-year student.
She's in charge of publicity.
ユアチューブの動画も300万再生
She's gotten three million views
on YourTube,
and they say she's sure to make it big.
メジャーデビューしたら
大ヒット確実っていわれてる
こんなふうに たまに
学内ライブが開かれるんだけど
Sometimes, she does concerts at school,
ファンクラブ会員でないと
but she's so popular, unless you're
in her fan club, you can't get in.
まずチケットが取れないくらい
人気でさ
ウフフ お詳しいんですね
- You know a lot about her, huh?
- As a classmate, I want to support her,
アハハ
同級生としては
応援したいところだけど
会費が高くて
- but the club fees are expensive.
- Thanks, everybody!
（ユメミ）
みんな ありがと〜
気に入ったら
応援 拡散 よろしく！
If you enjoyed it, click "like" and spread
the word! Share me with your friends!
私をシェアしてね！
あら？
Huh?
これは…
What's this?
〜
President!
（清華(さやか)）会長！
（綺羅莉(きらり)）あら 清華
Oh, Sayaka.
一体 どこへ行かれるのですか？
Where are you going?
私に行き先もお伝えくださらず
You didn't tell me.
I'll be leaving the school for a while.
There's something I have to do.
しばらく学園を空けるわ
ちょっとした用事があってね
But now's not a good time.
何もこのような時に！
実は 昨日
生志摩(いきしま)さんが蛇喰(じゃばみ)夢子に…
Yesterday, Ikishima and Yumeko Jabami--
（清華）聞いてるわ
I heard.
That's why I have to take care of this.
だから 用事ができたの
（清華）あっ
あとのことは
適当に処理しておいて
You can deal with the rest
however you wish.
任せたわよ
- I'm counting on you.
- But... I need you here...
（清華）そんな！
会長がいらっしゃらなければ
お待ちください！
- Please wait!
- That's enough.
くどい
あっ
（清華）
あれから もう１週間になる
It's been a week since then.
生徒会は決して 一枚岩ではない
The student council isn't always united.
Some plot to increase their power.
権力を志向する者
保身を旨とする者
Some just want to protect themselves.
Some pursue pleasure.
快楽を追及する者
意図が読めない者
Some are inscrutable.
私たちを つなぐのは
The only thing that ties us together
is our power as the student council...
会長の絶対権力を
よりどころとする—
which comes from the authority
of the president.
生徒会役員としての権威
しかし蛇喰夢子が現れたことで
事態は揺れ動いている
But the appearance of Yumeko Jabami
is changing all that.
（豆生田(まにゅうだ)）
生志摩が醜態をさらした日から
It's been a week
since Ikishima embarrassed herself.
１週間
会長は学園に登校していない
And the student council president
hasn't come to school.
なぜだ？
- Why?
- Well...
それは…
私も知らされておりません
I haven't been told.
（るな）ふ〜ん
Yeah? I was sure she'd have told you.
てっきり清華ちゃんには
話してると思ったんだけどね
ニャハハハハ！
（豆生田）ならば しかたない
Then I suppose we'll have to decide
我々だけでも
家畜に負けた２人の処遇を
what to do with the two
who lost to the house pets ourselves.
決めようじゃないか
（清華）
生志摩さんも西洞院(にしのとういん)さんも
Neither Ikishima nor Nishinotoin lost.
負けてはいらっしゃいません！
（豆生田）
会長の助力と敵の情けで
体面を保っただけだろう
They saved face with the help of
the president and the pity of their enemy.
（清華）え…
（豆生田）
校内中に うわさは広がっている
The rumors are spreading
throughout the school,
生徒会の威信は ガタ落ちだ
and our reputation is in the gutter.
ふがいない
It's pathetic. What makes you think
you can even come here?
どの面下げて
役員に居座っている？
Manyuda! It's inappropriate to speak
to a third-year student that way.
豆生田さん！
３年生に向かって僭越(せんえつ)です！
この学園に
僭越などという概念はない
The concept of "inappropriate"
doesn't exist in this school.
会長のそばにいるお前が
いちばん分かっているはずだぞ
You're the closest to the president.
You should understand better than anyone,
Sayaka Igarashi.
五十嵐(いがらし)清華！
あっ！
（妄(みだり)）
じゃあ お前が夢子とやってみろよ
You try and have at it with Yumeko.
フッ
なぜ俺が家畜ごときに
労を負わなければならんのだ？
Why do I have to try for a house pet?
夢子はなあ
Yumeko's got guts, a sharp eye...
度胸と洞察力 仲間への信頼
trust in her companion,
everything she needs.
必要なものを全て兼ね備えている
そして何よりも
And more than anything, those eyes!
あの目！
あれを思うだけで あたしは…
Just thinking of them makes me...
ウヒヒ ヒヒヒ ヘヘ…
生志摩さん まだ会議の途中ですよ
Ikishima, we're still in the middle
of our conference.
Bathroom.
ト イ レ
（豆生田）
変人のたわ言は
聞いていられないな
It's not worth listening
to the ramblings of a pervert.
（百合子(ゆりこ)）生志摩さんの評価は
Her appraisal isn't wrong.
あながち おかしくありませんわ
Yumeko Jabami is a house pet,
and that's what makes her so terrifying.
蛇喰夢子は家畜…
だからこそ おぞましい
If she uses her right
to challenge the president to a match...
彼女が会長に対し
公式戦の権利を行使すれば
depending on what the game is...
勝負の内容いかんによっては…
The president becomes a house pet.
It's the same for anybody, if they lose.
会長が家畜
あっ
（るな）
負ければ誰でも同じだからね
そんなことは 絶対にさせません！
I'll never let that happen!
わたくしも反対ですわ
I'm opposed to it.
We should recover the debt we're owed
to decrease the amount of money she has.
それよりも 資金を削(そ)ぐために
債務を回収するというのは？
忘れたのか？
Did you forget?
The president forbids that.
それは会長に禁じられている
しかもヤツには
人生計画表が出ていただろう？
She has a life plan drawn up for her.
YUMEKO JABAMI
INVESTIGATIVE REPORT
（ユメミ）うん 合格かな
Yes, I suppose she passes.
Leave Yumeko to me!
夢子ちゃんのことは 私に任せて！
THE GIRL WHO DANCES LOVE
（豆生田）
夢見弖 お前…
- Yumemite, you...
- Yumemite...
（清華）
夢見弖さん…
私が夢子ちゃんとやるよ！
I'll do it with Yumeko.
なるほど
I see.
確かにお前なら 蛇喰夢子を
徹底的におとしめる舞台を
It'd be simple for you to make a stage
that would crush Yumeko Jabami.
つくりやすいな
Right? I want to go big
if we're going to do it, though.
（ユメミ）でしょ？
（清華）あ…
せっかくなら
ド派手にやりたいよね〜
I want your help, Manyuda.
豆生田君にも 手伝ってほしいな
Very well. I'll ensure
that all preparations are made.
いいだろう
この企画の手配
全て俺が引き受ける
お待ちください
Wait! We should wait
for the president's orders.
会長のご指示を…
（清華）
ダ… ダメだ
No. I can't stop them on my own.
私では 抑えられない
そもそも 会長のご意思が
どこにあるのか 私には…
I don't even know
what the president wants.
（ユメミ）ウフフ 大丈夫だって
It's fine!
私たち２年生に任せておいて
Leave it to us second-year students.
そろそろ生徒会も
次の代のこと 考えなくちゃね
The student council should start thinking
about the next generation soon, right?
ウフフ…
（鈴井）あ…
Did something good happen to her?
（芽亜里(めあり)）
何か いいことでもあったの？
（鈴井）さ… さあ
I don't know.
She's been like this all day.
朝からずっと こんな感じなんだ
やっぱり あの手紙に
何か書いてあったのかな？
Was there something in that letter?
手紙？
Letter?
（伊月(いつき)）蛇喰先輩
Jabami-senpai...
お久しぶりです
It's been a long time. I'm Itsuki Sumeragi
with the Year One, Flower Class.
１年華(はな)組の皇(すめらぎ) 伊月です！
ジャ〜ン！
静風堂(せいふうどう)の和風モンブラン
Ta-da!
Japanese-style Mont Blanc from Seifudo.
I brought it as a present.
差し入れで〜す！
あっ それ うちの…
That's our...
おいしいんですよ〜！
It's so good!
知ってるわよ
I know you. You got fired by
the student council a few days ago, right?
あなた 先日
生徒会をクビになったんでしょ？
で 今度は夢子の弱みでも握って
So, is the plan now to find some dirt
on Yumeko and get your job back?
それを手土産に
返り咲こうって腹かしら？
浅はか〜
How obvious!
いや… やだな
Oh, no, of course not.
そんなわけ ないじゃないですか
アハハ
（芽亜里）ふ〜ん？
あ…
うっ
Fine.
分かりました　分かりましたよ
腹割って話しますよ
I'll tell you everything.
（伊月）私の父…
My father...
（芽亜里）
日本有数のトイメーカーの社長よね
The CEO of one of Japan's
biggest toymakers, right?
将来が約束されてて 羨ましいわ
I'm jealous that your future
is so assured.
それが… そうもいかないんですよ
It's not like that, though.
My father is a stern and practical man.
父は厳格な合理主義者
私は生徒会役員となり
He told me to join the student council
政財界との強いコネを作れ
と言われて
and develop connections
to the political and financial worlds.
この学園に入った
That's why I came here.
If I can't do that, he might disown me!
それができなければ
最悪 勘当もありえるんですよ
Jabami-senpai, is it true that you want
to be student council president?
蛇喰先輩！
生徒会長の座を
狙っているというのは
本当ですか？
（鈴井･芽亜里）あっ
It's a rumor I heard. The students,
particularly the house pets, are hopeful.
（伊月）うわさです
生徒たち 特に家畜の間で
期待混じりに語られているうわさ
蛇喰先輩が債務整理大集会で
大金を得たにもかかわらず
Despite the money you won at the Debt
Settlement Party, you remain a house pet.
家畜で居続けるのは
Because you want to challenge
the president to a match and win her seat.
生徒会長と会長の座を賭けた
公式戦をするためだって
（鈴井･芽亜里）え？
（鈴井）
夢子は ただ…
Yumeko is just gambling
because she wants to.
自分のやりたいように
ギャンブルをしてきただけだ
なのに
But...
いつの間にか 夢子を中心に
学園全体が動き始めている
at some point, the whole school
started to revolve around Yumeko.
そのうわさが本当だとすれば
If that rumor is true,
there's only one path for me to take.
私が取る道は ひとつしかない
蛇喰先輩に
生徒会長になってもらったうえで
I have to have you
become student council president.
Then let me join the student council.
私を生徒会役員にしてもらう！
そのためなら
どんな協力も惜しみません
I'll do whatever it takes for that.
これが うそ偽りない私の思惑です
That's my plan. I'm not hiding it at all.
どうか…
Please, let me join you.
私をお仲間に加えてください
（夢子）もちろん歓迎ですよ
（伊月）え？
Of course, you're welcome! I don't know
about being the student council president,
（夢子）
生徒会長うんぬんは ともかく
一緒にギャンブルを楽しんだ仲
じゃないですか
but we both gambled together, didn't we?
ひっ… あっ
（夢子）
私たち もうお友達でしょう？
We're friends now, right?
は？ そ… そうですね
That's right.
（芽亜里）あ〜 あ〜
（芽亜里）
頭ん中 お花畑か こいつ
Is her head filled with flowers?
（売り子Ａ）ＤＶＤはこちらです
- DVDs on sale!
- Her new CD is here!
（売り子Ｂ）
新作のＣＤは こちらになります
どうぞ〜
プロマイド もう完売です
（真能寺(しんのうじ)）いつもながら
Another amazing concert!
すばらしいライブでした！
真能寺君 今日も来てくれたんだ
Shinnoji, you came to see me again!
Of course!
（真能寺）当然です
ファンクラブ会長としては
１回たりとも欠かせませんから！
As president of your fan club,
I'll never miss one!
ただ 今日は
But the clapping was off
during "Gambling Girl" today, wasn't it?
“ギャンブリング･ガール”での
合いの手のタイミングが
甘かったですね
- I'll make sure it's corrected.
- Don't be too harsh on them.
今後は 徹底させますので！
ウフフ ほどほどにね
（真能寺）いえいえ！
I'll make sure to train them properly
since your major debut is coming up.
メジャーデビューを控えた
ユメミちゃんのファンとして
ふさわしいよう教育します
それが会長としての責任ですから！
That's my responsibility as president.
People like that are skipping out on
their quota of 100 YourTube views a day!
大体そういう輩(やから)は
ノルマである
ユアチューブ１日100再生も
サボってるんですよ！
僕みたいにスマホ５台持ちで
やれとまでは言いませんが
I won't insist they do it
with five smartphones like I do,
せめて100再生くらい
やってもらわないと
but they need at least 100 plays a day
or they can't say they're a fan!
ユメミちゃんのファンとは
言えませんから！
アッハハハ…
DRESSING ROOM
ガラ ガラ ガラ… ペッ
ゴホ ゴホ
ハア ハア ハア
気持ち悪(わり)いんだよ
あの豚ども！
Those pigs are disgusting!
ハア ハア ハア…
（沙織(さおり)）せめて
Should we at least stop
the post-concert meet-and-greet?
ライブ後の握手会だけでも
取りやめにする？
（ユメミ）ダメ
No. It can't just be the concerts.
ライブだけじゃなくて
個人的なつながりを得てこそ
Relating to them one-on-one
is what makes them die-hard fans.
あいつらは太客になるんだから
それにしたって…
But still...
（ユメミ）大丈夫よ 沙織
It's fine, Saori. This is nothing
if it helps me with my dream.
夢のためなら
屁(へ)でもないわ
このくらい
平気でこなせなきゃ
If I can't do this,
I can never make my dream come true.
とても
達成できないもの
それより夢子への申し込みは
いつするの？
Anyway, when are you sending Yumeko
the message?
（沙織）明日にでも
I can do it tomorrow.
Manyuda has prepared the budget.
豆生田さんの手配で
予算は確保できたから
（ユメミ）そう 楽しみだわ
I see. I can't wait.
アハッ
Yumeko's going to bet her life!
夢子ちゃんには
人生を賭けてもらうよ！
What? You're gambling with Yumemite?
（鈴井）
え！ 夢見弖さんとギャンブル？
Yes. Her manager just came by.
はい
先ほどマネージャーさんが
いらっしゃって
（鈴井）
何てことだ
Oh, no. Yumeko has taken out one member
of the student council after another.
夢子は生徒会役員を
次々と破ってきた
間違いなく夢子は
I'm sure they're after her.
狙われている！
（ユメミ）
それじゃ 豆生田君
あと よろしくね
Okay, Manyuda, take care of the rest.
（豆生田）任せろ
Leave it to me.
会長のいない今が
絶好のチャンスなんだ
With the president gone,
now's the perfect chance
俺たち２年生が
生徒会の実権を握る な…
for us second-year students
to take power in the student council.
俺はイベントの準備に入る
I'll get the event ready.
Make sure you don't let Jabami beat you.
蛇喰に足元をすくわれないように
気をつけろよ
（ユメミ）
エヘヘ 豆生田君たら
心配性なんだから
You're such a worrywart, Manyuda.
（夢子）
こちらの鈴井さんも
一緒でよろしいですか？
May Ryota come with me?
（沙織）男性ですか？
A boy? Well, I guess it's okay.
まあ いいでしょう
（夢子）
ありがとうございます　では！
Thank you. Okay!
（沙織）
ちょ… 待ってください！
Wait!
今 許可を得ますから！
I'll get permission now.
すみません 気がせいてしまって
I'm sorry. I was just in a hurry.
（沙織）
入室前に
身体検査をさせてください
Let me pat you down before you enter.
まれに控え室に
Once in a while, people try to set up
cameras and listening devices in her room.
カメラや盗聴器を仕掛けようとする
不届き者がいるんです
（夢子）ええ 結構ですよ
Yes, that's fine.
いらっしゃい　私 夢見弖ユメミ
Welcome. I'm Yumemi Yumemite.
I'm an idol.
アイドルやってます
（鈴井）はあ〜
（夢子）はじめまして 夢見弖さん
Hello, Yumemite.
（ユメミ）
ん… そちらの男の子は？
Who's that boy?
あっ え… えっと
２年華組 鈴…
I'm Ryota,
with the Year Two, Flower Class--
（ユメミ）鈴井涼太(りょうた)君！
Ryota Suzui!
You came to my concert, right?
ライブに来てくれたことあるよね！
去年の学園祭ライブ
３(スリー)デイズの２日目！
The second day
of the three-day school festival concert!
（鈴井）
え？ よ… よく覚えてますね
I'm amazed you remember that.
That was a long time ago.
随分 前のことなのに
（ユメミ）
ファンの子の名前と顔は
全部 覚えてるよ
I remember the names and faces
of all my fans.
アイドルとして 当然だよ！
Every good idol does.
それで 私と
どのようなギャンブルを？
So, how are you going to gamble with me?
Oh, right. Gambling.
そうそう ギャンブルね
これを見て
- Look at this.
- "Top Idol Match"?
一流アイドル決定戦？
It sounds like a variety program.
何か いかにも
バラエティ番組でやりそうな…
It was actually a plan for a TV show,
本当は テレビ用の企画なんだけど
夢子ちゃんと共演できるなら
やりたいな〜って
but if I can do it with you,
that'd be great.
ライブのあとに みんなの前でね
In front of everyone, after the concert.
お邪魔にならなければ
よいのですが…
- I hope I don't get in the way.
- Of course you won't.
邪魔なわけないよ
This concert is our chance
to pick a new member.
だって このライブは
新メンバー選考を兼ねてるからね
（鈴井）へえ？
（ユメミ）賭け金は５千万円
The bet is 50 million yen.
それだけあれば 夢子ちゃんは
家畜を脱せるでしょ？
That's enough to get you out
of being a house pet, right?
（夢子）ええ
- Yes.
- And...
（ユメミ）で 私が勝ったら
if I win, of course,
your debt amount will increase.
当然 夢子ちゃんの借金が
増えちゃうんだけど
そのときは…
And if that happens...
you'll form an idol unit with me.
私とアイドルユニットを
組んでもらうわ！
I'll have your life plan changed
to reflect that.
（ユメミ）
人生計画表を
そういうふうに変えてもらうの
ユニット名も決めてるんだ
その名も
I've even got a unit name.
It's "Dreaming Creaming Sisters"!
〝どり〜みん くり〜みん
しすた〜ず〞
What?
（鈴井）え… ハ… ハズッ
We both have "yume,"
or "dream" in our names.
２人とも
名前に“夢”の字が入ってる！
これって運命だと思わない？
Don't you think that's fate?
でもね アイドルは
楽しいことばかりじゃないよ
But being an idol isn't always fun.
レッスンは厳しいし
私生活はないも同然
Lessons are hard,
and you don't have a private life.
もちろん恋愛なんて もってのほか
And of course,
romance is out of the question.
You'll have to adjust
your whole life around being an idol.
夢子ちゃんもアイドルに
人生 賭けてもらうよ！
I see.
（夢子）なるほど…
それにしても
But why are you so willing to be an idol?
なぜ そうまでしてアイドルを？
もちろん ファンの笑顔のため
Of course, for the smiles of my fans.
そんな建て前は よしてください
Don't lie to me.
夢見弖さんは
ファンが嫌いなんでしょう？
You hate your fans, right?
あ…
何言ってるの？
What are you saying? That's impossible.
そんなわけないでしょ〜
Oh, you're sure?
（夢子）あら そうですか？
Then what is this?
では これは何でしょう？
（ユメミ）え？
え!?
（夢子）
ちょっと読んでみましょう
Maybe I'll read a little!
“愛するユメミちゃんへ”
"To my beloved Yumemi. Thanks for your
fun concerts! You always do a great job!
“いつも
楽しいライブをありがとう”
“そして お疲れさま”
“最近は
ユアチューブの人気もすごくて”
Lately, you've been so popular
on YourTube,
“ファンクラブ会長としても
鼻が高いです”
I'm very proud to head your fan club.
“エッヘン！”
“でも 古参のファンとしては
ちょっと さみしいかな”
But as a long-time fan, I'm a little sad.
“括弧 笑い”
“最近は 勉強が忙しいんだけど”
Lately, I've been busy studying,
but when I see how hard you're working..."
“ユメミちゃんが
頑張っている姿を見てると…”
もういい！
Enough!
ユメミ
Yumemi...
（ユメミ）あんたの言うとおりよ
You're right.
だったら何？
So, what?
If you're continuing being an idol
even though you hate your fans,
ファンが嫌いなのに
アイドルを続けているということは
you must have some kind of strong goal.
よほど強い目的を
お持ちなのでしょう
それをお聞きしないことには
とても私は…
If I don't know what that is, then I...
アカデミー賞が欲しいの
I want an Academy Award.
I've always wanted one since I was little.
小さいころから憧れだった
才能と実力と運に恵まれた者のみが
歩くことを許された空間
A space where only those with talent,
skill, and luck are allowed to walk.
全世界が
その一挙手一投足に注目する
The whole world watching their every move.
I want to be one of the flowers
on the red carpet too!
私もレッドカーペットを彩る
一輪の花になりたい
役者事務所に登録して
毎日レッスンをこなして
I joined an agency,
took lessons every day,
同期の中で 最も早く
テレビのレギュラーをもらった
and got a regular spot on a TV show
faster than anybody.
でも気付いたの
But I realized it was taking too long.
これじゃ遅いって
このまま 順調にいったとしても
Even if things kept going well,
there was no guarantee
I could get to the top of Japan.
この日本という狭い国ですら
トップに立てる保証はない！
ハリウッド大作で
重要な役を得るには
If I wanted a major role
in a Hollywood movie...
I needed a different approach.
もっと違うアプローチがいる
それが この学園
And that was this school...
and being an idol!
そしてアイドルをやること！
With the power of this school, I could
easily become the most popular idol.
学園の力があれば
アイドルとして天下を取る
なんて訳ない！
人気絶頂のときに
女優に転身すれば
If I became an actress
at the peak of my popularity,
一足飛びに
日本でトップクラスに立てる！
I could instantly be one
of the top actresses in Japan.
そこまでいけば
At that point,
being in a Hollywood movie would be easy.
ハリウッド映画に出演することも
難しくない！
（夢子）すばらしい目標です
That's splendid. That's why you're
doing this even though you hate it, huh?
そのために
嫌でも続けているんですね
ファンとの交流を
- Interacting with your fans?
- That's right.
（ユメミ）そうよ
They're ugly, but that's okay.
あいつら
見た目が悪いのは まあいいわ
自分の見場より
私に金を使ってるってことだから
That means they're spending money on me
instead of their own looks.
でも…
But... why the hell are they dancing
like madmen at my concerts?
ライブで踊り狂ってるのは
何なわけ？
踊ってる暇あったら
私の歌 聞けよ！
If you've got time to dance,
listen to my songs!
なんで お前らが
Why are you sweating more than I am?
いちばん
汗かいてんだよ！
その汗まみれの手で
握手 求めてくんな
Stop trying to shake my hand
when yours is sweaty! It's disgusting!
気持ち悪(わり)いんだよ！
ハア…
（夢子）
ウフフッ
アイドルも大変なんですね
It's hard being an idol, huh?
覚悟しておいて
Get ready. You're gonna do it too.
あなたもやるのよ
（夢子）お話を聞くかぎり
From what you've said,
I don't want to be an idol at all.
私は全くアイドルになりたいと
思いません
But...
ですが…
そのような職業に人生を捧げる
dedicating my life to a job like that...
It's a wonderful risk!
それってとっても
すてきなリスクですね
私が手取り足取り 教えてあげる
I'll teach you all you need to know.
But it's not a fun game
（夢子）
でも 私だけでなく
お互いに人生を賭けなければ
unless we're both
betting our lives, right?
ギャンブルの面白みに
欠けますよね
え？
はっ
何を…
What are you...?
はっ！
え？
今のやり取り
録音させていただきました
I took the liberty
of recording this conversation.
正直 破れた手紙だけでは
弱いと思っていたんです
To be honest, I didn't think
the letter would be good enough.
これが公開されれば
If this goes public,
your life as an idol is over, right?
アイドルとしての人生は
終わってしまいますよね
（ユメミの声）
なんで お前らが
いちばん汗かいてんだよ！
Why are you sweating more than I am?
その汗まみれの手で
握手 求めてくんな
Stop trying to shake my hands
when yours are sweaty! It's disgusting!
気持ち悪(わり)いんだよ！
夢子…
- Yumeko...
- Why? Why does Saori have that?
なんで なんで
沙織がそんな物を!?
No, I...
いや… 違… あ…
は！ あのとき！
That was when...
（夢子）夢見弖さんには
Let's bet this voice recorder, too.
このボイスレコーダーも
賭けてもらいましょう
（沙織）
渡せ！ あっ あっ あっ…
Give me that!
（夢子）ご安心を
Don't worry. I wouldn't do anything
so crude as make copies.
コピーなんて
不粋なマネはしませんから
私はギャンブルができれば
それでいいんです
If I can gamble,
that's good enough for me.
くっ
それでは当日
楽しみにしておりますね
I'll look forward to the day of the game.
あ… えっと… あの…
Well...
ゆ… 夢子！
Yumeko!
はあ… ああ
ごめんなさい
本当に ごめんなさい
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
私のせいでユメミの…
私たちの夢が！
Because of me, your dream... our dream...
（ユメミ）ウッ ククク… クク…
クク… ククッ フフフ…
アッハハハハ！
上等だよ 上等！
Fine, then!
蛇喰夢子！
Yumeko Jabami!
I'll make you regret messing with me!
私をナメたこと
絶対に後悔させてやる！
Yumeko?
（鈴井）夢子
そのボイスレコーダー…
That voice recorder...
（夢子）
破かれたファンレターと
一緒に入ってました
It was in there along with the fan letter,
as if to say, "Use this to threaten her."
これを使って脅せと言わんばかりに
一体 誰の仕業でしょうね
I wonder who put it there.
（沙織）分からない
I don't know.
あの手紙は 焼却処分しようと
ここにしまっておいたはず
I put that letter here to burn it later.
戸締まりも厳重にしてるのに…
And I always lock the door tightly.
（ユメミ）
私や沙織の前で
盗めるとは思えないわ
I can't believe anyone could steal it
when we were here.
つまり 犯人は
マスターキーを持っている者
In other words,
the one who did it had a master key.
（ピー）
（留守番電話）
発信音のあとに
メッセージをどうぞ
Please leave a message after the beep.
（るな）
あ〜 もしもし 会長 生きてる？
Hello? President, you alive?
こっちは ちょっと
面白いことになってるよ〜
Things are getting kind of fun here.
早く帰ってこないと
学園がどうなっても知らないよ！
You'd better come back soon,
or who knows what will happen
to the school?
（曲のラスト部分）
"OF COURSE YOU CAN" BATTLE!
（歓声）
“あなたをブラックジャック”
でした！
That was "I'll Blackjack You"!
みんな ありがと〜！
Thank you, everyone!
（観客）最高！
You're the best!
（ユメミ）残念ながら
I'm afraid that's all
for today's concert, but...
今日のライブは
これでおしまいだけど
（観客）え〜！
What?
予告どおり これから
ユニットメンバーの選考会をやるね
Just like I said,
I'm about to pick a new member!
（観客）ウォ〜！
It's finally time for Yumeko to appear.
いよいよ 夢子の出番だ！
っていうか
Wait, do we really have to stay
until the end?
ホントに 最後まで
いなくちゃダメなの？
だから 別に
来てもらわなくてよかったんです
We didn't need you here anyway.
蛇喰先輩たっての頼みで
人数分 用意しただけですから
I just got enough tickets for everyone
because Jabami-senpai insisted.
（鈴井）早乙女(さおとめ)
Saotome, these premium tickets
このプレミアチケットは
ホントに普通じゃ
手に入らない物なんだ
aren't usually something
you're able to get.
（伊月）まったく！
Do you know how hard I had to work
to get them from a fan club member?
どれだけ苦労して
ファンクラブ会員から
譲ってもらったと
思ってるんですか？
（芽亜里）分かった 分かった
Fine. You already told me.
それ もう聞いたから
I'll introduce you!
Or do you know her already?
それじゃ 紹介します
みんな知ってるかな？
先月 転校してきてから
快進撃を続けている—
She's made quite a name for herself
since coming to school last month.
百花王(ひゃっかおう)学園２年 華組
Hyakkao Academy, Year Two, Flower Class,
蛇喰夢子ちゃんです！
Yumeko Jabami!
（鈴井）うわ〜！
（伊月）
こうしてみると
やっぱりかわいいですね〜
Jabami-senpai looks so cute
in that outfit!
蛇喰先輩
夢子ちゃん 意気込みをどうぞ
Tell us how you're feeling, Yumeko!
ウフフ
こんな機会は初めてなので
緊張しますが
I've never had an opportunity like this,
so I'm nervous,
精いっぱい
楽しませていただきます
- but I'll enjoy myself as much as I can.
- Okay! Here we go!
オッケ〜
それじゃ いくよ〜！
一流アイドル決定戦
「バトっていいとも！」
It's time for the "Top Idol Match
'Of Course You Can' Battle!"
Let's get started!
始まりま〜す！
〜
（真能寺）
ユメミちゃん 好きだ〜！
- Yumemi! We love you!
- You can only win by dumb luck!
（鈴井）
そんなの
ただの運勝負じゃないか！
（夢子）
ただの運 結構じゃないですか
- Just luck. That's a perfect game!
- Yumemi's future will be over.
（沙織）
ユメミの将来が終わる…
（ユメミ）
そして 今まで
Thank you
for cheering me on till now.
応援してくれて ありがとう
EPISODE 9: DREAMING GIRL